A little kindness makes a world of difference.
Won't You Be My Neighbor? is a documentary film directed by Morgan Neville.
For more than thirty years, and through his television program, Fred Rogers (1928-2003), host, producer, writer and pianist,
accompanied by his puppets and his many friends, spoke directly to young children about some of life's most important issues.
Self - TV Producer, played by Margaret Whitmer.
Self - Journalist and Fred's Friend, played by Tom Junod.
Self - Fred's Wife, played by Joanne Rogers.
Self - Fred's Son, played by Jim Rogers.
Self - Fred's Biographer, played by Max King.
Self - Child Development Advisor, played by Hedda Sharapan.
Won't You Be My Neighbor?
is a 2018 American documentary film about the life and guiding philosophy of Fred Rogers, the
host and creator of Mister Rogers' Neighborhood, directed by Morgan Neville.
The trailer for the film debuted on what would have been
Rogers' 90th birthday, March 20, 2018.
The film premiered at the 2018 Sundance Film Festival and was
released in the United States on June 8, 2018.
It received acclaim from critics and audiences and grossed over $22 million, becoming the top-grossing
biographical documentary ever produced and the 12th largest-grossing documentary ever produced.
It was nominated for numerous awards, won the Independent Spirit Award for Best Documentary
Feature, and was chosen by Time magazine as one of its top ten films of 2018.
The film explores themes of puppeteer, biography, based
on true story, childhood, puppet show.